晚上好 女士们
Good evening, ladies.
别想
No.
麦克斯 你这是干嘛
Max, what are you doing?
我知道这一带的奇葩多
I know this neighborhood is a circus,
但咱们这窗口要成怪胎秀了
but our window's becoming a freak show.
麦克斯 之前那个大妈
Max, I don't think that bearded lady earlier
不是故意留胡子的吧
was doing it on purpose.
那只是更年期导致的
It's more of a menopause thing.
他才没钱买小蛋糕
He can't afford a cupcake.
他连两个轮子的单车都没钱买
He can't even afford two wheels.
您好 请问需要什么
Hi. What can I get you?
我要一个香草口味
I'll take one vanilla.
四块钱
That'll be $4.
女士 其实呢
Actually, madam,
我今晚打算用一首诗付账
tonight I'll be paying with a poem.
人家要用诗付账呢 女士
We're paying with a poem, madam.
我拉 影推
I pull. Shadows push.
那时我是个孩子
I was a child then.
给老娘吐出来
Spit it out.
你想要诗是吧
Hey, you want a poem?
玫瑰花是红的 紫罗兰是蓝的
Roses are red, violets are blue,
找份工作吧
Get a job!
以及另一个轮子
And another wheel!
感觉真爽
That felt good.
我理解你为啥爱这样了
I get why you do that.
等你有机会赏人脸上一拳吧
Wait till you get actual fist-to-face contact.
那才是真的过瘾
That's a real high.
欢迎光临威廉斯堡餐厅 迪克
Welcome to the Williamsburg diner, Deke.
你怎么知道我们餐厅的 《厨房噩梦》吗
Where'd you hear about us? Kitchen Nightmares?
麦克斯 说正事吧
Okay, Max, let's get to it.
我们得决定学校的烘培作业
We have to decide what we're each gonna make
我们分别要做什么
for our pastry school homework.
或者按照老规矩 我不做
Or true to form, I'll blow it off,
揍你一顿 拿你的去交
beat you up, and take yours.
我的大脑袋里目前想到了焦糖肉桂卷
Of the top of my giant head, I'm thinking sticky buns.
迪克的暗黑肉棒卷
Deke's dark sticky buns.
我们是来谈甜点 不是你裤裆里的事
We're talking about dessert, not what's going on in your pants.
我本来想做布朗尼蛋糕的
Well, I would've baked brownies
后来想起来原料被我抽完了[大麻]
until I remembered I smoked all the ingredients.
天啊 你猜谁又发短信给我了
Oh, my God, guess who texted me again.
朱迪·丹奇女爵士吗
Dame Judi Dench?
她给我发过无数次短信了
Dame Judes texts me all the time.
她超饥渴啊
She's thirsty.
她是朱迪·丹奇女爵"湿"吧
More like "Damn, Judi Dench."
迪克 我不知道你来了
Oh, hi, Deke. Didn't know you were here.
你真是无处不在啊
You're everywhere.
烘焙学校里
Pastry school,
之后还要跟麦克斯在电话中聊学校
on the phone with Max talking about pastry school,
现在还坐在这里讨论与受人敬爱的
and now here at the counter talking about elder sex
老年舞台剧 电影女演员的性爱
with a beloved star of stage and screen.
-你简直就像... -啥
- You're like-- - What?
被困在查宁的身材里的丹泽尔吗
Denzel Washington trapped in Channing Tatum's body?
常有人这么说
I get that a lot.
言归正传 麦克斯
Anyway, Max,
这是尼可拉斯主厨
this is the fourth time Chef Nicolas
第四次私下发短信给我了
has texted me outside of school.
这次还发了个视频呢 你看
And this time he sent me a video. Look.
卡洛琳 然后把油从平底锅里舀...
Then, Caroline, you spoon the fat from the pan...
是他敞开衣服做饭呢
It's him making breakfast with his shirt open.
你觉得这是什么意思
What do you think it means?
他不怕煎培根时被油溅到
That he doesn't have a fear of bacon splatters.
他完全是在跟我调情吧
He's totally flirting with me, right?
绝对的 尼可拉斯大厨对你有性趣
Totally. Chef Nicolas is hot for ya.
你在身边时 他就得别两层围裙
He has to double up on aprons when you're around,
你懂我的意思吧
Know what I'm sayin'?
迪克 这是闺蜜间的私密谈话
Deke, this is just private best friend stuff between girls.
跟你完全没有关系
You know, that you're not a part of.
也能跟我没关系吗
Can I not be a part of it?
尼可拉斯主厨是你们的老师
And since Chef Nicolas is your teacher
我也是学校的职员
and I work at the school,
这件事能保持我们三个知道就好吗
I'd appreciate it if we kept this just between us three.
我也知道 我从你后面偷看到了
And me. I saw it over your shoulder.
完全比不上我的
Doesn't hold a candle
光下身肉卷系列视频啊
to my series of pantless meatloaf videos.
肉卷 上菜
Meatloaf. Pick up.
好了 麦克斯 有时间靠着休息
Okay, okay, Max, if you have time to lean,
就有时间打扫
you have time to clean.
如果我有时间揍你一拳
And if I have time to give you a punch,
我们就有时间吃饭
we have time to have lunch.
麦克斯 我们该帮他找妈妈吗
Max, should we help him find his mom?
惨了 现在有两只了
Oh, no, now there's two of them.
跟小魔怪一样
Like gremlins.
快干活 这里是餐厅 不是自习室
Now, come on. This is a diner, not study hall.
你在上班呢
You're working.
我称在这里做的事情为
I call it "spiritually dying,"
"灵魂慢慢死去" 但叫"工作"也可以啦
but working's a good word for what we do here too.
我们可以明晚边喝点小酒边谈啊
We could figure it out tomorrow night over some drinks.
喝几杯白气泡酒 明白我意思吗
Couple of white wine spritzers. Know what I'm sayin'?
你是跟闺蜜在海边度假的寡妇娘们吗
That you're a recently-widowed woman on a girls' trip in Boca?
水喝完了 我可以走了
Well, I already ate my water, so I'm good to go.
爷要闪人啦
I am out the door.
我叫迪克 再见啦 麦克斯
Hi, I'm Deke. Bye, Max.
他是你的朋友啊
Oh, he's your friend?
我本来以为他是我跟
For a minute I thought he was that kid
琳达·伊万斯生的私生子呢
I had out of wedlock with Linda Evans.
你为什么在里面打混不干活
Okay, why are you in here not working?
你为啥打混不叫上我
And why are you doing it without me?
你看 我跟尼可拉斯在发短信聊
Look, I've been texting with Nicolas.
他很饥渴
He thirstay.
他想在他明天晚饭后找我喝一杯
He wants me to meet him for a drink after his dinner tomorrow.
晚饭后 你懂意思吧
After his dinner. You know what that means.
他觉得他不用请你吃晚饭
That he thinks he doesn't have to buy you dinner
就能把你变炮友吗
before he makes you his slampiece?
晚饭后约就是约炮啦
After dinner is a booty call.
或者是法文里的"打炮之约"
Or as they say in France, "A call du bootay."
所以你明晚得一起来
So I need you to hang out with me,
因为到时候如果没借口离开的话
because if I don't have anything else to do at that time,
我会没理由拒绝他
I won't be able to resist him.
我觉得他不会吧
I don't see it.
可能是因为他从没拿刀逼我做爱
Maybe because he never pulled a knife on me,
但在我看来 他是无性生物
but to me he's, like, asexual.
是无性不欢的生物吧
Yeah, like a sexual object.
好吧 我答应迪克要帮忙他弄作业了
Okay, well, I told Deke I'd help him with his homework,
你可以跟我们一起
so you can hang out with us.
跟迪克一起吗
Hang out with Deke?
我又不爱看《布偶秀》 干嘛跟他一起
I didn't even like The Muppets on TV.
行吧 我有事做也好
But fine, it'll-- it'll keep me busy,
因为呢 麦克斯 每当尼可拉斯看着我
Because Max, when Nicolas looks at me,
我的里面都会有反应
it does something to my insides,
而我想要先确定关系
and I want this to be a relationship
才能让他对我的"里面"干嘛干嘛
before he does something to my insides.
你再继续说你的"里面"
If you keep talking about your insides,
我就要踹你的"外面"了
I'm gonna kick you on your outsides.
所以我的甜点作业呢...
Okay, so as far as my dessert homework goes--
他又给我发短信了
He just texted me again.
"你在何处"就是你在哪
"Ou es-tu?" "Where are you?"
他用了"你"不是"您"
And he used "tu" not "vous."
感情到那儿了
We've gone there.
那你人怎么还在这儿啊
Then why are you still here?
因为我还不能去那儿啊 我还没准备好
Because I can't go there, Max, I'm not ready.
阴毛没刮吗
Oh, wax situation?
男人才不在乎呢
Guys don't care about that.
我的甜点作业呢 我发愤图强
So as far as my dessert goes, I went all-out
真的去查了些资料
and actually did some real research.
你搜了有名字歧义的甜点吗
You googled desserts with dirty names?
没错
Correcto.
比我想象中的难下决定啊
And it was harder to pick one than I thought.
比如说有"洞洞"蛋糕啊 "金手指"
I mean, you got your bundt cake, your lady fingers,
金桔派
Kumquat pie...
金[精]桔[阴吹]
"Kum" and "quat"
这么明显的同音双关 我怎么一直没发现
It was right there the whole time. How could I not see it?
在仔细思考后 我有了答案
So I dug deep, and I have the winner.
"在嘴咬嚼"[焦糖奶油松饼]
Croquembouche.
完全不知道那是啥 但一听就是个骚货
I don't know what that is, but she sounds like a whore.
是一种传统的法国结婚蛋糕
It's a traditional French wedding cake
用满是香草奶油的泡芙叠塔
with vanilla cream-filled profiteroles
由这里唯一不读烘焙学校的人说出
Said the only person here not in pastry school.
不错啊 我本来都不知道是啥
Oh, cool. I didn't know what it was.
我可以帮忙啊
Maybe I can help.
我刚好知道尼可拉斯很爱梨子鞑靼塔
I happen to know Nicolas loves a pear tarte tatin.
哒哒哒 才不要呢
Ta-ta-tan! No.
我还以为跟你们一起出来能分心不紧张
I thought I'd distract myself by going out with you guys,
但感觉这像是我高中时
but it feels like the day in high school
为了赚点街头名声 故意跟抽烟屁孩混
I hung out with the smokers for street cred.
我以前也是为了午餐钱
And I used to hang out with rich geeks like you
故意跟你这样的有钱书呆玩啊
when I needed lunch money.
我要发消息找他了
I'm texting Nicolas.
什么 是你自己说不想让他以为能当炮友
What? You said you didn't want him to think you were
才跟过来的 真谢谢你啊 这位小姐
up for a wham-bam, thank you, mademoiselle.
你说得对 麦克斯 我不应该找他
You're right, Max. I shouldn't text him.
他又发短信来了 喝一杯多少钱
He just texted me again. What's one drink?
真的吗 那你赶紧找他来吧
It is? Yeah, you better text him.
我们需要个大人来付酒钱
We need a grown-up to pay for the drinks.
我就说我跟朋友在一起 他可以来喝一杯
I'll just say I'm with friends, and he can join for a drink.
正常人都是这么做的吧 我忘了
Isn't that what people do? I forget.
我好久没做过正常人或做过啥体面事了
I haven't been a person or done anything in so long.
也好久没"做"过正常人了
Or done a person in so long.
我不会让事情发展到那地步
I won't let it get that far.
应该说是你不能放任他那样
And by that I mean you won't.
我会给你信号 你就说我们还有事得先走
I'll give you a signal and then you'll say we have to go.
什么信号 他完全插进去吗
What's the signal? Full penetration?
是在那之前
No, before that.
"头"刚进入时吗
So just the tip?
我就眨眨眼吧
I think I'll just wink.
所以做"在嘴咬嚼"吗
So, croquembouche?
我假装不了在聊天
I can't pretend to talk.
希望他的舌头有戴避孕措施吧
I hope his tongue is wearing protection.
我们让你们感到不自在了吗
Are we making you uncomfortable?
没有没有 只是我看黄片时
No, no, it's just that I usually like to fast-forward
通常习惯快进跳过接吻的部分
through the kissing parts when I watch porn.
别这样 麦克斯 我们就开心一下而已嘛
Come on, relax, Max. We're just having some fun.
只是你是我们的老师
It's just that you're our teacher,
而你的口水都到她嘴里了
and your spittle is all over her mouth.
我们又不在教室里 这里有面粉糊或碗吗
We're not in class. Do you see batter or bowls?
我们希望不用见到任何蛋蛋[碗]
Well, we're hoping not to see any balls.
我看见了其中一颗的轮廓
I see the outline of one of 'em.
现在不用把我当成老师
Just don't think of me as a teacher right now.
但我学到了不少呢
Well, I'm kind of learning a lot.
对一个不打算上床的人来说
You know, for someone who wasn't gonna have sex,
她已经在做爱了
She's having sex.
我要走了
I'm leaving.
自从我妈跟我毕业舞伴在礼车上做爱
I haven't felt this awkward since my mom had sex
还叫我开车后 我就再也没这么尴尬过了
with my prom date in the limo and made me drive.
感觉你妈是个辣妈啊
Your mom sounds cool.
别这样 你不能走 我们才刚到呢
Come on, you can't leave. We just got here.
她也快要"到"了 我可不想看
Well, she's about to get there, and I don't wanna see it.
我们也可以亲热啊
Well, we can make out.
你想跟我亲热吗
You wanna make out? With me?
不是啦 就搞笑亲热
No, a comedy make-out.
比如这样
You know, like...
你让我看得好有兴致啊
Well, you make it look so tempting.
来嘛 会很好玩的
Come on, it'll be hilarious.
让我的嘴成为你舌头的避风港
Let my mouth be your tongue's panic room.
也可以给尼可拉斯大厨指点一番
And Chef Nicolas could use a few pointers.
是啊 人家技术可"差"了
Yeah, he's really bad at it.
好吧 有何不可
All right, why not?
说不定还能引起他们注意
It might even get their attention.
数到三开始
On the count of three.
一 二
One, two...
他们看了吗
Did they look?
他忙着在她"三"垒打转呢
No, he's busy rounding third.
轮到我了
My turn.
麦克斯 这是怎么了
Max, what's happening?
他在舔你的脸
He's licking your face.
不要管他们了
Leave them alone.
迪克感觉也很懂行
Deke seems to know what he's doing.
客气客气
Respect.
虽然我很不想搞笑亲热完就跑
Well, hate to comedy make out and run,
但我的心已经到了甜甜圈店里
but, well, I'm already mentally at Yummy Donuts
尝试疯狂吃掉脑海里的这画面
trying to binge eat this image out of my mind.
等等 麦克斯 信号来了
Hold on, Max. The signal.
你看 这就是为啥我不爱当人闺蜜
See, this is why I don't do girlfriend.
走啦 我们得先走 去办事之类的
Come on, we have somewhere to go or be, something like that.
我们得走了
We have to go.
再见啦
See you later.
再会
Au revoir.
近来如何
'sup?
没啥大事
Not much.
那你呢
'sup with you?
抱歉 我得接个电话 我老婆打来
Sorry, I have to get this. It's my wife.
老妹啊
Girrrl...
我完全忘记告诉你了
Oh, I totally forgot to tell you.
你亲热的技术烂爆了
You're terrible at making out.
我没爸爸 所以没人教我
Well, I never had a father to teach me.
胖子姐们
Hey, big Mary.
走廊吃午餐 真"羡慕"你们
Hallway lunch. Love that for you.
还有你
And you.
如果不是我把及时把你拉走
This could've been your walk of shame right now
现在你就是做完羞愧地走进来 眨眼妹
if I hadn't stepped in, winky.
是啊 昨晚局面有点失控
Yes, last night got a little out of hand.
是几乎在你"掌中"吧
Oh, it was pretty much in your hand.
才不是呢 麦克斯
No, it was not, Max.
没错 可能是鉴赏性地摸了一下
Yes, there might have been a tasteful graze,
只是为了估计他下面的尺寸有多欧洲
just to figure out how European he was down there.
好消息是 "头顶"不是软趴趴的贝雷帽
Good news, it's not wearing a floppy beret.
所以我们会发展成为完美的童话式爱情
So we are right on track for a perfect fairy-tale romance.
是啊 美国公主和法国阳具
Yeah, the princess and the penis.
餐厅见 麦克斯 再见 朋友们
See you at the diner, Max. Au revoir, mes amis.
我有件事要告诉你
I have to kinda tell you something
你要答应我
that you have to promise you kind of
绝对不会告诉卡洛琳
definitely won't tell Caroline.
你是想告诉我 她说法语时
Are you about to tell me that when she speaks French
你也会有想把头用力
it makes you want to slam your head
撞向玻璃窗的冲动吗
through that plate-glass window too?
我想说的是 他结婚了
Heh. Well, the thing is he's married.
他结婚了 你怎么知道的
He's married? How do you know?
他又没戴戒指 而且他不像是已婚麻木男啊
He's not wearing a ring, and he doesn't seem dead inside.
昨晚你们走后 他老婆打来电话
His wife called him after you guys left.
他怎么能这样呢
How could he do that?
他是法国人嘛
He's French?
而且还不告诉卡洛琳
And not tell Caroline.
他是法国人嘛
He's French?
真是个混蛋
What a jerk.
法国人嘛
Fronch?
我现在就要去告诉她
I'm telling her right now.
等等 等等 麦克斯 帮我个忙
Wait, wait, wait, Max, do me a favor.
能不能等我交了我的作业再说
Can you just wait until after I turn in my croquembouche?
我跟"让我很烦咖啡厅"老师关系很不好
I'm already on thin ice with "au bon pain in my ass."
太过分了
This sucks.
他都结婚了 而卡洛琳的思维又很奇怪
He's married, and Caroline has this weird thing in her head
她非得跟没老婆的人结婚
that she has to marry someone who isn't married.
早安 碧碧 你好吗
Bonjour, Bebe. Ca va?
天啊
Oh, boy.
我不是很擅长外语
I'm not really good with any languages.
医生说是因为我被三辆车撞过
They think it's because I got hit by three cars.
提个醒 如果你被车撞 别立刻起身
FYI, if you ever get hit, just stay down.
对了
Well, guess what.
我给咱俩准备了沙拉 闺蜜午餐
I got you and me salads. Girls' lunch.
我通常都是在阴暗处偷吃
Well, I usually just have Peanut butter
花生酱和饼干
and crackers in the dark.
我慕名沙拉已久 一直很想试试
I hear so much about salad I've always wanted to try it.
坐下吧 一起吃沙拉
Sure. Sit. Have some salad.
你和我 就咱俩
You and me, me and you.
增进对彼此的了解
Getting to know more about each other.
碧碧 我想知道尼古拉斯的一切
So Bebe, tell me everything about Nicolas.
他人超棒
He's the best.
他拥有狗狗的心灵和眼睛
He has the heart and eyes of a dog.
尼古拉斯 你觉得他现在在哪
So Nicolas, where do you think he is?
他刚说有个午餐约会
He just said he had a lunch date.
约会
Date?
"约会"这个词
Did he use the word "date,"
是他说的 还是你说的
or are you just using the word "Date"?
我意思是 他不像是有约会对象啊
I mean, it's not like he's dating anyone.
有吗
Is he?
没有 他怎么会在跟人约会
No, why would he be dating anyone?
就是 他怎么会在跟人约会
Exactly, why would he be dating anyone?
对啊 他都结婚了
Yeah, I mean, he's married.
结婚了
Married?
沙拉尝起来就像生菜啊
You know, salad tastes just like lettuce.
这件事说出来你都不会信
You are not going to believe this.
肯达尔·詹娜要申请大学吗
Kendall Jenner is applying to colleges?
拜托 麦克斯 有可能吗
Come on, Max, no.
尼古拉斯 听好了 已经结婚了
Nicolas is--and get ready-- married.
我居然跟一位已婚男人接吻 太有失身份了
I kissed a married man. I'm so mortified.
千万不要告诉别人我跟一个已婚男人接吻
Please don't ever tell anyone I kissed a married man.
好的 我不会告诉任何人
Okay, I won't tell anyone.
告诉任何人啥
Tell anyone what?
卡洛琳跟一个已婚男人接吻
Caroline kissed a married man.
千万不要告诉别人哦
But don't tell anyone.
好吧 我要公开说明下
All right, I want to go on the record
我事先并不知道
that I didn't know.
我的人生规划中并不包括跟已婚男人接吻
Kissing a married man has never been in my life plan.
这既不我的愿景板上 也不在我的梦景里
It's not on my vision board or in my dreamscape.
我不是那种人
I am not that kind of person.
但她是那种既拥有愿景板
But she is the kind of person who has a vision board
又说出"梦景"这个词的人 大家快来鄙视她
and says "dreamscape," So let's judge her on that.
我不会鄙视你的 卡洛琳
I won't judge you, Caroline.
我曾跟一位已婚女子约会
I once went out with a married woman.
直到她的配偶打了我一顿
I didn't know she was married
我才知道她已经结婚了
until her spouse came and beat me up.
拉拉们可猛了
Lesbians are strong.
看待已婚和未婚 不要这么美国化
Listen, married, not married, don't be so American.
在波兰 我们的结婚誓词是
You know, in Poland, the wedding vows say,
"你愿意娶这个女人
"Do you take this woman...
和其他几个吗"
and maybe some others?"
我不是波兰人 也还没变拉拉
Well, not Polish, and not a lesbian yet.
所以我非常郁闷
So I'm very upset.
麦克斯 你为什么光站在这儿
And, Max, why are you just standing there?
你不发表发表意见吗
Why haven't you said anything?
我早知道了
I kind of knew.
站住 你早就知道他结婚了吗
Wait. You kind of knew he was married?
你早就知道 却没有早告诉我
You kind of knew and didn't kind of tell me?
你算哪门子朋友啊
What kind of friend are you?
我也是刚知道
I just found out myself.
那你为什么不告诉我
Well, then why didn't you tell me?
我是想告诉你 但迪克让我
I was going to, but then Deke asked me not to
等他交了作业再说
until he handed in his homework.
而且我怕你会哭
And also I thought you might cry.
你是不想让我难过吗
Oh, and you didn't want to upset me?
不 我只是不想遭殃
Nah, I didn't want to deal with it.
因为每次你哭 你不是只哭一段
'cause when you cry, you don't just cry once.
每次都哭够六个阶段
It's like a six-cry thing.
一开始是号啕大哭 接着是呜咽不语
You've got the first shock cry, the silent cry,
再接着痛哭流涕 然后是因为哭而哭
the ugly cry, the cry because you're crying,
再然后是你刚说完不哭 又开始哭
the cry after you say you're not gonna cry anymore,
至于最后那阶段 估计都是被我弄哭的
and then the final cry, which is probably my fault.
你错了 麦克斯 我这次不会哭
Well, you're wrong, Max, I'm not gonna cry over this,
因为我对他的感情还没有这么深
because I haven't gone far enough down the road.
没错 虽然我是开始幻想我们的未来了
Yes, I was just beginning to think about our future,
但我还没那么全心投入
but I'm not that invested.
那这是什么
Then what's this?
-我的小本子 -没错
- My dupe pad. - That's right.
瞧瞧我在后面发现了什么
And look what I found written on the back.
"卡洛琳和尼古拉斯·圣克劳"
"Caroline and Nicolas Saintcroix."
"圣克劳夫妇"
"Mr. And Mrs. Saintcroix."
"卡洛琳·圣克劳"
"Caroline Saintcroix."
那只是犯傻而已 每个怀春少女都会这样
That's just being silly. Every girl does that.
大姐 你都40岁了
You're 40.
天啊 又沉又重
Oh, man, this is heavy.
我知道 非常沉重
I know, very heavy.
回到学校 我必须面对
We're back here, and I have to deal with the fact
我被一个已婚男人隔衣干搞的事实
that I was dry-humped by a married man.
不是 他是说他的甜点很重
No, I think he meant his dessert is heavy.
但没错 你的心情很复杂
But yeah, you got a lot going on.
你想让我们帮你做什么
So what do you want us to do?
打他一顿吗 还是玩爆他的菊花
Should we throw down? Mess his ass up?
踢他的脸一脚
Kick him in the face?
还是什么都不做 免得被踢出学校
Or just ignore it so I don't get kicked out of school?
不用了 晚点我自己找尼古拉斯
No, I'll deal with Nicolas later.
你确定吗
You sure?
我可是一直都想杀一个法国佬
'cause I've always wanted to kill a French person.
再杀一次
Again.
谢啦 但你别管了 我能处理
Thanks, but stay out of it. I've got this.
我要把他碎尸万段
I'm gonna rip him a new one.
-早安 卡洛琳 -早啊 尼古拉斯
- Bonjour, Caroline. - Bonjour, Nicolas.
那不算碎尸 碎花都算不上
That wasn't a rip. Wasn't even a tear.
你们俩 快进去
Go, go, you two.
给新鲜出炉的大洞洞蛋糕让路
Got a big, hot bundt here.
去吧 别迟到了
Go, go, don't be late.
你确定这是"在嘴咬嚼"吗
You sure that's a croquembouche?
看起来就像是土狼的粪堆
'cause it looks like a coyote poop tree.
卡洛琳 你能进去帮我看着电话吗
Caroline, can you watch the phones for me
我要传尼古拉斯老婆的留言给他
while I give Chef Nicolas this note from his wife?
要不这样 我给他好了
You know what? I'll give it to him.
反正我也有事要找他
I have something I have to say to him anyway.
下次闺蜜午餐 你吃过三明治吗
Oh, for next girls' lunch, have you ever had sandwiches?
因为我在考虑要不要尝尝
'cause I'm thinking of trying one.
不是你
Not you.
你做得到 你做得到
You have got this. You have got this.
你都甩过肯尼迪家的高富帅了
You broke up with a Kennedy cousin.
你能做到
You can do this.
卡洛琳 找我有事吗
Caroline, do you need something?
我只是来送电话留言给你
I just wanted to give you this phone message you just got.
是你老婆留的
From your wife.
你妻子 朱丽叶
From your wife. Juliette.
-我知道她的名字 -你都结婚了
- I know her name. - You're married.
是啊 刚才留言的就是我老婆啊
Yes, you just got a message from my wife.
我觉得是不是咱俩语言不通有歧义
I feel like something's getting lost in the translation here,
那恕我直言 我们之间完了
So let me be clear. It's over between us.
为什么
Why?
为什么 因为你有老婆了
Why? Because you're married.
我知道我有老婆啊 但是为什么
Again, I know that. But why?
你老问"为什么"干嘛
What--what do you mean "why"?
原因就是你已经结婚了 您结婚了
Why? Because you are married. Vous est marie!
注意 我刚没用"你"
And note, I did not use "tu"
因为我们回到要用"您"这样正式的关系
because we are back on the more formal "vous" terms.
卡洛琳 我的老婆在法国
Look, Caroline, my wife is in France,
而且我们达成了共识
and we have an understanding.
我对你们的共识表示完全不能理解
Well, I'm having a hard time understanding any of this.
不管你和朱丽叶的协议是什么
And whatever arrangement you and Juliette have,
反正我们玩完了
it's over between you and me.
给
Here.
你生气的时候好可爱
You are very cute when you're angry.
是吗
I am?
老实说 你一直很可爱
Actually, you are very cute all the time.
可爱又性感
Cute and sexy.
从见到你那一刻 我就想...
From the moment I saw you, I wanted to...
吻上你的唇
put my lips onto yours.
是吗
You did?
是的
Yes.
卡洛琳 你是一个聪明性感又可口的女人
Caroline, you are a smart, sexy, delicious woman.
现在我已经吻过...
And now that I've kissed--
你眼睛里有东西吗
Do you have something in your eye?
没有 没有
No, no, no, no, no.
从来不是你
It's never you!
不好意思 到底什么了
I'm sorry, what is happening?
尼古拉斯主厨 你得赶紧进去
Chef Nicolas, uh, you need to get back in there
因为脖子有纹身的大厨
Because the Chef with the neck tattoo
想拿从店里买来的提拉米苏充数
is trying to pass off a store-bought tiramisu.
每年都有一个
There is one every year.
卡洛琳
Caroline.
你没事吧 他说什么了
Are you okay? What did he say?
他说他结婚了 反正一片混乱
He said he's married, and it's confusing,
而我很可口
and I'm delicious.
好吧 他已婚 事混乱 你可口
Okay, well, he's married, it's confusing, and you're delicious.
所以你是可口·圣克劳太太
So you're Mrs. Delicious Saintcroix.
你们结束了 对吗
So it's over, right?
当然结束了 没有大吵大闹 没有哭哭啼啼
Yeah, of course it's over. No drama, no more crying.
我绝不会跟已婚男人在一起
I would never be with a married man.
是啊 那更像是我会做的事
Yeah, that's more my thing.
天啊 麦克斯
Oh, my God, Max,
你知道我刚意识到什么吗
you know what I just realized?
我也曾说过 我绝不会当服务员
I once said I would never be a waitress.
老妹啊
Girrrl...